<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Give support on Student Wellbeing</title>
    <link>https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeing/give_support/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Give support on Student Wellbeing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeing/give_support/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Helping a colleague in distress</title>
      <link>https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeing/give_support/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeing/give_support/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>All UM faculty and staff play an important role in promoting a positive culture of well-being and support. If you see a colleague showing signs of distress, use the strategies and resources listed on the &amp;ldquo;Employee wellness&amp;rdquo; UM Intranet site on the &amp;ldquo;Helping a colleague in distress&amp;rdquo; page to offer support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to help a student in distress</title>
      <link>https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeing/give_support/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeing/give_support/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>This resource for faculty and staff will aid in supporting students who are experiencing difficult and distressing mental health challenges. Access the full student distress guide on UM Intranet under “Employee resources” and “Health and wellness.” (Access UM Intranet with your @umanitoba.ca employee email address.)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leaders supporting employee wellness</title>
      <link>https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeing/give_support/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeing/give_support/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>While the pensioner of Ghent and his eminence were exchanging very low bows and a few words in voices still lower, a man of lofty stature, with a large face and broad shoulders, presented himself, in order to enter abreast with Guillaume Rym; one would have pronounced him a bull-dog by the side of a fox. His felt doublet and leather jerkin made a spot on the velvet and silk which surrounded him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Success Through Wellness Grants (previous)</title>
      <link>https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeing/give_support/chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeing/give_support/chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>Wellness and mental health grants were provided through UM’s Success Through Wellness Grant program, launched in the fall of 2017. Thirteen grants of up to $10,000 funded projects fostering positive mental health and well-being at UM were awarded funding in 2018 and 2020. Learn more about the funded projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Success Through Wellness Implementation Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeing/give_support/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeing/give_support/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Create an action plan for your unit, department, team or group to bring mental health and well-being to the forefront of your learning and workplace. This practical how-to guide focuses on three main themes: community health and well-being; support, understanding and inclusion; and balance and flexibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wellness and Mental Health Grants</title>
      <link>https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeing/give_support/chapter-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeing/give_support/chapter-5/</guid>
      <description>UM wellness and mental health grants engage the community to foster positive mental health and well-being and create a supportive, responsive and inclusive learning and work environment through new initiatives, activities, events and projects. Learn more about the UM Wellness and Mental Health Grants (WMHG) program.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
